

#### BUILDING FOR THE WEB

## Victor Isaac

in https://linkedin.com/in/victor-isaac



https://twitter.com/IsaacVictron

Phone

+2348124182627

**Email** 

tamsvictorisaac@outlook.com

Location

Lagos, Nigeria

#### About me

I am an Enthusiastic and ambitious programmer with over 2 years of experience using various programming languages and web frameworks to build and maintain websites and webapps. Experience in designing and developing sites from concept to roll out. grasp of various programming languages like C#, Python, JavaScript and framework options like ASP.NETCore, Django etc. including development platforms and security requirements.

#### **Experience**

## Freelance Web Developer, KCLStores, FeronAuto, Agro-Matic, Sureseis, StBarnanbasFoams)

2019 - Present | Port Harcourt,

Nigeria

- \* I have worked on a few web projects contracted to me by startups and businesses
- \* Discussed site and app requirements with clients to produce actionable development plans and budgets.
- Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with HTML, JavaScript, Python
- \* Designed, implemented, and monitored web pages, plugins, and functionality for continuous improvement.

#### Web Developer, Agro-Matic/ Web Dev PH

2021 - 2022 | Port Harcourt, Nigeria

- \* Successfully worked with a team in creating, designing, and launching www.agromaticstaking.farm, a crypto staking platform for the Agro-Matic cryptocurrency
- \* Contributed to team success by completing jobs quickly and accurately.
- Developed strong cooperative relationships with coworkers and managers.
- Sought out ways to go above and beyond job requirements.

#### Education

### Interlink Polytechnic

2019 - 2022 | Ijebu-Jesa, Nigeria

Computer Science, HND

Built a facial recognition attendance system for my final year project

### Port-Harcourt Polytechnic

Computer Engineering, ND

2016 – 2019 | Port Harcourt, Nigeria

- Graduated with a 3.3/4.0 Upper Credit
- Built a real-time computer for my ND projectz
- Assisted lecturers and lab facilitators in building embedded systems

## Skills

Blockchains | Ethereum | Solidity | Django Web Framework | .NET Framework | C# | Python | Web Development | Embedded System | Computer Science | Web3 | MVC

# Languages

English (Intermediate)